<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Cayman</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Cayman</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>How to download speech in Windows 10</title><link>/how-to-download-speech/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/how-to-download-speech/</guid><description>Navigate to Settings. You can get there by clicking the Settings icon on the start menu. Click Time &amp;amp; language Select Region &amp;amp; language from the left pane. Select a new region from the pulldown menu. As of this writing, Speech is only available in the United State, United Kingdom, Italy, France, Spain, Germany and China. Click Add a language under the Languages subhead. Select the your language.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Thank you for using Convert Text to Speech app! Here we describe what information we collect, why we collect it and how we handle it.
TL;DR We may collect anonymous statistics about your usage such as error, crash. Some 3rd parties may know your statistics. We never share your data with 3rd parties except to help us deliver our services. These are the key points, if you need detail, keep reading.</description></item></channel></rss>